A mysterious group lives in the Dayin Dynasty.
They are born with special abilities.
Eagle vision,
invisibility,
and earth-tunneling.
They are mutants different from ordinary people.
Among them,
a branch of the Helian clan,
due to their skill in finding gold
and gold mines,
were reduced to gold mine slaves.
The Shen clan, born with eagle vision and skilled in archery,
formed the Shenji Camp.
Half of the world's mutants belonged to it.
The royal Ji clan feared their power.
To uproot the Shen family's influence,
the elderly emperor forced the Shen family's only daughter,
Shen Mingyue, to marry him as empress.
He bestowed the royal surname Ji upon her
to cut off the Shen family's lineage.
The gold embezzlement case implicates the entire Dayin court.
Now that the ledger is in my hands,
many people will surely be on pins and needles.
Could the ledger for the gold case be on her?
Newcomer?
Yes.
One of Mother's people.
What did she ask you to do?
The gold case concerns the Northern Border and the Crown Prince.
The Crown Prince is already watching you with the crystal stone.
The Shen family's Eagle Eye is indeed impressive.
Greetings, Your Highness.
I wonder if the matter of the ledger
is known to Ji Hongzhen.
Ji Hongzhen, I already have the ledger of the gold case.
Once I find out your connection to this case,
even if you are the Crown Prince.
Even your father can't protect you.
Get out.
Yes.
Smells good.
You may step down too.
Yes.
Mother, you are so uninhibited.
You completely disregard past affections and the royal family's dignity.
Do you think my father is dead?
Your father is now bedridden with a stroke.
What's the difference between that and being dead?
Right.
You are in your prime, Mother.
If you are too lonely to bear,
why not come to me?
If they can do it,
why can't I?
As long as your father is still alive,
you will always be the Crown Prince.
And I will always be your mother.
What a pity.
You won't be my mother much longer.
Do you think you can beat your father?
How would I know without trying?
Assassin!
Guards!
No matter how you struggle,
or how unwilling you are,
you will end up being my woman.
You can't escape.
Ji Hongzhen,
don't forget your status.
You are the Crown Prince,
and I am the Empress.
If you dare to barge into my bedchamber casually
and speak so insolently again,
next time, my arrow
will aim for your head.
Your Highness,
His Majesty was prepared.
This old bastard is really tough to kill.
Give orders for tonight's plan.
If there are any more mistakes,
you don't have to come back.
Yes.
Ji Mingyue.
There is no woman I want
that I cannot have.
The Crown Prince has always coveted you.
But you are his mother in name.
He
is truly a madman.
Thankfully, you adopted the Ninth Prince as soon as you entered the palace,
which has spared you a lot of trouble.
It's just too unfair to you.
The royal family fears the Shen family.
That's why the Emperor married me.
If the Shen family doesn't yield,
and if the General's Manor loses its power,
the Divine Machine Camp, which relies on us to survive,
will immediately become
ravenous wolves turning against the Shen family.
I understand.
But this
is too unfair to you.
In this world,
where is there any fairness?
Strange.
Why is the smoke from this censer so heavy?
The Huo family,
the Northern Frontier,
Ji Hongzhen,
and the Helian clan involved in gold mining...
It seems a storm is brewing in Great Yin.
Go invite Huo Lingyu.
I have something to ask her.
Yes.
How dare you show off such a trivial invisibility spell
in front of me?
The eyes break through all obstacles,
and the magic weapon breaks through all spells.
The weapon forged by Shen's Magic Weapon Camp
is indeed the natural enemy of strangers.
The magic weapon breaks through all spells.
Your Highness, you've been hit by my immobilizing spell.
How should I break this spell?
I must find the account book quickly.
Otherwise,
I'm afraid I won't be able to return to the Northern Realm alive.
I've searched everywhere,
but I couldn't find the account book.
It should be on her.
I don't want to do anything,
just looking for something.
You found me so quickly.
I wonder whose subordinate you are.
It seems I guessed right.
You are indeed here for the account book.
You can actually break my immobilizing spell?
No,
it doesn't look like Shen's spell.
My subordinates will be here soon.
I'll give you three moves.
Within three moves,
if you can't take me down,
I'll kill you.
I never wanted your life.
Why are your moves so aggressive?
Otherwise,
should I give you another chance to cast the immobilizing spell?
Excuse me.
You lecher,
you're so shameless.
The incense burner has been tampered with.
Ji Hongzhen, that bastard.
Wushan Xing.
The poisoned person will lose all their spells within the time it takes an incense stick to burn.
They will die if they are not detoxified.
What kind of move is this?
Oh no,
this medicine triggered the Qianji poison in my body to flare up early.
With the two poisons combined,
I'm afraid I'll die here today.
So hot.
Hurry!
His Highness ordered,
we must find Her Highness.
Hurry,
search here too.
Hurry!
They all say I'm a bewitching demon queen.
No matter who this person is,
it's going to be true this time.